paxum.com 2013-11-24

# Privacy

Privacy Policy

(Effective as of October, 2009)

PAXUM values your trust and respects your expectation of privacy. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal financial information in accordance with our established policies and in compliance with applicable law. This document outlines the manner in which we collect, use and maintain the nonpublic personal information we receive regarding you.

VISITORS TO OUR WEB SITE.

Visitors to our web site remain anonymous, unless they register for a service or otherwise elect to disclose their identity to us. Although we do not collect personally-identifying information about persons who simply visit our site, we do collect certain limited information about visitors, such as their IP address (a numeric address assigned automatically to computers when they access the Internet). We also attempt to place "cookies" on a computer to track a visitor's use of our web site. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your hard drive. It takes up very little room on your system and helps us to customize our site and make its navigation easier for you. We sometimes use cookies to help estimate the number of visitors to our site and to determine which areas are the most popular. Unless you register with us for a service, the cookie does not provide us with any personally identifying information about you, such as your name or address. Our website is not directed at individuals under 18 years of age.

OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU.

We collect nonpublic personal information about you in order to administer our business, process your transactions, understand your needs, and provide you with products and services. We obtain nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: Information (such as your name, Social Security number, postal address, email address, telephone number and date of birth) you provide to us when applying and in requests by telephone, through this web site, and through other channels.

Information (such as your card balance, funds loading history, parties to transactions, and card usage) about your transactions with us, joint marketers, or others; and

Information we receive from other sources (such as a consumer reporting agency) in the process of verifying your application information or other information required in the decision process).

OUR DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION. 

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies (including affiliates) that perform services on our behalf, including those who assist us in preparing and distributing cardholder communications, and responding to customer inquiries. We will also disclose information about your card, membership, and transactions: (a) to service your account; (b) where it is necessary or helpful to effect, process, confirm or enforce a transaction you request or your membership rights and obligations; (c) to verify the existence and availability of funds associated with your card; (d) to comply with legal process, such as subpoenas and court orders; (e) to law enforcement authorities if we believe a crime has been committed; (f) to our agents, service providers and auditors, and (g) if you give us your consent. We may also disclose non public personal information about you as permitted by law.

OTHER DISCLOSURES.

We may enter into arrangements with non-affiliated parties, such as financial service providers, lenders, insurance providers and agencies, card issuers, retailers and direct marketers, in order to provide you with special offers that we believe may be of value to you. We may disclose contact information to those parties who may want to offer their products and services to you.

USE OF AGENTS. 

We may use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

USE OF SERVICE PROVIDERS.

We use other third parties to provide statistical tracking and advertising effectiveness for our web site. When you sign up for PAXUM services, we may share information such as your name and address and other information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

SPECIAL NOTICE FOR VERMONT AND CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS. 

We will not disclosure information about consumers with a Vermont or California mailing address to unaffiliated third parties without your written authorization, unless otherwise permitted by law. Disclosures that are permitted under Vermont and California law without written authorization include, among others, disclosures necessary to effect, administer or enforce a transaction you request; disclosures to our authorized agents and service providers; disclosures permitted or required by law or disclosures to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.

Written authorizations from Vermont residents may be delivered to us by email at support@paxum.com. Vermont authorizations must contain your name, address and signature and your authorization to disclose your information to nonaffiliated parties. You may revoke your consent at any time by sending us written notice by mail or email at the addresses above.

California residents should contact us at the addresses provided above for instructions on how to deliver their authorizations.
